download.hr 2018-12-26

# Download.hr Privacy Policy

[](https://www.download.hr/) Download.hr Privacy Policy 

### Privacy and Cookies Policy

**The privacy of our visitors to Download.hr is important to us.**

At Download.hr, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit download.hr, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies**  
Download.hr may use the following cookies:

\- UI Customization cookies (to store information such as user's interface language)  
\- Technical cookies (for certain site functionalities wich depends on users input etc.)  
\- Cookies for authentication (enables registered user to log on Download.hr. We support Google+ and Facebook login options which may use their own cookies)  
\- Analytics cookies (for example Google Analytics and AddThis service. The cookies are stored directly by the analytical providers)  
\- Advertising Cookie

We use third-party advertising companies (such us Google AdSense) to serve ads and collect information when users visit our site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements on our site, other websites and other forms of media about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, check out [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

You can set your browser to refuse or accept cookies, or set the browser so that cookies are automatically deleted once you close your browser, computer or device. You may change your cookies settings in browsers as follows:  
Google Chrome Settings > Privacy > Content Settings > Cookies  
Firefox Preferences > Privacy.  
Internet Explorer under Tools > Internet Options > Privacy > Advanced.  
Safari Preferences > Privacy.

By accessing this website for the first time, without previously giving your agree / consent to the use of cookies from Download.hr, you will see a window informing you of the use of cookies and where you can view this Privacy Policy. If you close the window and continue browsing, you agree / consent to the use of cookies and these will be installed on your computer or other browsing device. If you don't agree to our Privacy Polic please leave Download.hr.

**Children's Guidelines**  
Download.hr gives children under the age of 18 the ability to publicly post or distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consent. Please take proper measures if you do not wish your child to have access to public forums. We advise our users not to share personal information in a public forum.

**User accounts**  
Visitors can crete user account on Download.hr. Once user creates account he can't request it to be deleted but can change contact information such email.

If you feel that Download.hr is not following its privacy policy, you should first contact Download.hr.
